<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tom-show on Junyu Blog</title>
    <link>https://junyubian.github.io/tags/tom-show/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tom-show on Junyu Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://junyubian.github.io/tags/tom-show/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fluent Bit Client Notes</title>
      <link>https://junyubian.github.io/2023/11/07/Fluent-Bit-Notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://junyubian.github.io/2023/11/07/Fluent-Bit-Notes/</guid>
      <description>What is fluent bit Structural sketch How to set it up Through config file Though command line parameters Other ootes What is fluent bit One day, the Insurance Management System Tom built crashed. Good news is the system recovered through rebooting, bad news is Tom did not know what had gone wrong. Tom&amp;rsquo;s dad comes by and says to Tom &amp;ldquo;Fluent Bit is a telemetry agent designed to collect and process telemetry data from constrained systems to cloud infrastructures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurance Management System - Overview</title>
      <link>https://junyubian.github.io/2020/04/28/Insurance-Management-System---Overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://junyubian.github.io/2020/04/28/Insurance-Management-System---Overview/</guid>
      <description>In this series of blogs, we will talk about how to build a Insurance Management web application together with database system. Background Tom&amp;rsquo;s dad works in an insurance company. His work is to drop down who bought what kind of insurance, on which day does the customer receives an invoice, and on which day does the customer makes a payment. Oneday, Tom&amp;rsquo;s dad talks to Tom: &amp;ldquo;Oh Tom, you see</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KMP Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://junyubian.github.io/2020/04/17/KMP-Algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://junyubian.github.io/2020/04/17/KMP-Algorithm/</guid>
      <description>Background&amp;hellip; Once upon a time, Tom asked his father to find abab inside abcaabababaa.
Tom&amp;rsquo;s dad did this in a traditional way (brute force). He compared each character of the first string with each character of the second string. When he find one character not matching, for example, the third character in the second string in this case, he start again from the second character of the second string. It went on and on and on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
